homepowersolutions.org 2016-06-09

# Privacy Policy — Home Power Solutions

**PRIVACY POLICY for www.HomePowerSolutions.org**

At www.HomePowerSolutions.org we are committed to safeguarding and preserving the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy explains what happens to any personal data that you provide to us, or that we collect from you whilst you visit our site. We do update this Policy from time to time so please do review this Policy regularly.

**Information We Collect**

Like most websites, in running and maintaining www.HomePowerSolutions.org, we may collect and process the following data about you:

  1. Information about your use of our site including details of your visits such as pages viewed and the resources that you access. Such information includes traffic data, location data and other communication data.
  2. Information provided voluntarily by you. For example, when you register for information or make a purchase.
  3. Information that you provide when you communicate with us by any means.

**Use of Cookies**

We may use cookies where appropriate to gather information about your computer in order to assist us in improving our website. Cookies store information about visitors preferences, record specific information about which pages a user accesses or visits, and lets us customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have no control.  Such cookies (if used) would be downloaded once you click on advertisements on our website. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.HomePowerSolutions.org's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

You can adjust the settings on your computer to decline any cookies if you wish.  This can easily be done by activating the reject cookies setting on your computer.

**Use of Your Information**

We use the information that we collect from you to provide our services to you.  In addition to this we may use the information for one or more of the following purposes:

  1. To provide information to you that you request from us relating to our products or services.
  2. To provide information to you relating to other products that may be of interest to you. Such additional information will only be provided where you have consented to receive such information.
  3. To inform you of any changes to our website, services or goods and products.

If you have previously purchased goods or services from us we may provide to you details of similar goods or services, or other goods and services, that you may be interested in.

Where your consent has been provided in advance we may allow selected third parties to use your data to enable them to provide you with information regarding unrelated goods and services which we believe may interest you.  Where such consent has been provided it can be withdrawn by you at any time.

**Disclosing Your Information**

We will not disclose your personal information to any other party other than in accordance with this Privacy Policy and in the circumstances detailed below:

  1. In the event that we sell any or all of our business to the buyer.
  2. Where we are legally required by law to disclose your personal information.
  3. To further fraud protection and reduce the risk of fraud.

**Third Party Links**

On occasion we include links to third parties on this website. Where we provide a link it does not mean that we endorse or approve that site’s policy towards visitor privacy. You should review their privacy policy before sending them any personal data.

**Children’s Privacy**

Protecting children’s privacy is especially important to us. It is our policy to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and all other applicable laws. Therefore we restrict our Web site to persons eighteen years or older.

YOU MUST BE EIGHTEEN (18) YEARS OR OLDER TO ACCESS THIS WEB SITE. IF YOU ARE UNDER EIGHTEEN YEARS OF AGE, YOU ARE NOT PERMITTED TO ACCESS THIS WEB SITE FOR ANY REASON. DUE TO THE AGE RESTRICTIONS FOR USE OF THIS WEB SITE, NO INFORMATION OBTAINED BY THIS WEB SITE, FALLS WITHIN THE CHILDREN’S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT (COPPA) AND IS NOT MONITORED AS DOING SO.

**Our Company’s Commitment to Data Security:**

Services and Web sites we sponsor have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party “hackers” from illegally obtaining this information.

Where to Direct Questions About Our Privacy Policy: If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact us through the contact information provided on this Web site.

**Revisions to This Policy:**

Our company reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy, our Terms Of Service agreement, and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner, by updating this posting. Your use of this site after such changes are implemented constitutes your acknowledgement and acceptance of these changes. Please consult this privacy statement prior to every use for any changes.
